<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata><idinfo><smtype>1</smtype><citation><citeinfo><smcilnkh>false</smcilnkh><title>Middle Keys Juvenile Snapper Seine Sampling</title><origin>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission: Fish and Wildlife Research Institute: Finfish Research Program</origin><pubdate>Unpublished Material</pubdate><geoform>vector digital data</geoform><pubinfo><publish>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission-Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</publish><pubplace>St. Petersburg, FL</pubplace></pubinfo><onlink>http://myfwc.com/research</onlink><onlink>http://myfwc.com/research/saltwater/status-trends/finfish/</onlink><onlink>http://myfwc.com/research/gis</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><supplinf>Prior to July 1, 2004, the Fish and Wildlife Research Institute (FWRI) was known as the Florida Marine Research Institute (FMRI). The institute name has not been changed in historical data sets or references to work completed by the Florida Marine Research Institute. The institute name has been changed in references to ongoing research, new research, and contact information.</supplinf><abstract>The FWC: FWRI Finfish Research Program conducted a stratified-random designed study using 21.3m seines on the Atlantic side of the middle Keys in order to collect early life stages of snappers [Gray snapper (Lutjanus griseus), Mutton snapper (Lutjanus analis), Lane snapper (Lutjanus synagris), Schoolmaster snapper (Lutjanus apodus), and Yellowtail snapper (Ocyurus chrysurus)] in shallow near shore seagrass beds adjacent to beach fronts, and to describe their distribution and abundance.  Other species abundance information were collected and recorded in conjunction with this sampling effort.</abstract><purpose>This long-term seine monitoring program in shallow near shore seagrass beds will attempt to:
• Describe the distribution and abundance, species composition, size structure, and habitat usage of juvenile snapper species in the middle Florida Keys
• Develop a pre-recruit (juvenile) tuning index which may be used for stock assessments of snapper species.</purpose></descript><status><progress>In work</progress><update>Continually</update></status><accconst>These data are unrestricted.  Where possible, always acquire this dataset directly from FWC as other sources may have altered the original data.</accconst><useconst>Users are encouraged to read and fully comprehend the metadata record prior to using these data.  Please acknowledge the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission (FWC) as the data source for any products developed from these data. Users should be aware that comparison with other data sets for the same area may be inaccurate due to inconsistencies resulting from changes in mapping conventions, data collection techniques, and computer processes over time. FWC shall not be liable for improper or incorrect use of these data.</useconst><smbrowse>false</smbrowse><timeperd><current>ground condition</current><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20060614</begdate><enddate>20150420</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo></timeperd><datacred>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission : Fish and Wildlife Research Institute: South Florida Regional Lab Finfish Research Program</datacred><native>Microsoft Access</native><keywords><theme><themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Category</themekt><themekey>biota</themekey><themekey>environment</themekey><themekey>oceans</themekey></theme><place><placekt>FWC_Place</placekt><placekey>east coast of Florida</placekey><placekey>Florida</placekey><placekey>Florida Keys</placekey><placekey>Florida Keys National Marine Sanctuary</placekey><placekey>FWC Region-South</placekey><placekey>Middle Keys</placekey><placekey>south Florida</placekey></place><theme><themekt>FWC</themekt><themekey>biology</themekey><themekey>coastal</themekey><themekey>fish community</themekey><themekey>fisheries</themekey><themekey>GIS</themekey><themekey>Mangrove Snapper</themekey><themekey>national marine sanctuary</themekey><themekey>nets</themekey><themekey>other fish</themekey><themekey>other invertebrates</themekey><themekey>research</themekey></theme></keywords><secinfo><secsys>FWRI-DC</secsys><secclass>Available without restriction</secclass><sechandl>Available without restriction</sechandl></secinfo><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntorgp><cntorg>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission-Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</cntorg><cntper>Finfish Research Program</cntper></cntorgp><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>South Florida Regional Lab</address><address>2796 Overseas Highway 119</address><city>Marathon</city><state>Florida</state><postal>33050</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>(305) 289-2330</cntvoice></cntinfo></ptcontac><spdom><bounding><westbc>-81.113750</westbc><eastbc>-80.942133</eastbc><northbc>24.764333</northbc><southbc>24.685283</southbc></bounding></spdom></idinfo><dataqual><logic>After visual inspection, these data appear to be logically consistent.</logic><complete>These data are complete as of the 9/25/2015 delivery date to Chris Boland from Jeff Renchen, minus the Florida Keys Pilot Project (FKX Survey prefix) and the Marquesas pilot project (MQM Survey prefix).</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>All survey locations displayed within the sampling area, as depicted in the "Juvenile Snapper Seine Sampling Protocol" document provided by Jeff Renchen, of the Finfish Research Program.</horizpar></horizpa><vertacc><vertaccr>The vertical (Z) value of the survey location is reported from the "StartDepth" field of the records and measured in the field.  No StartDepths excede the 1.5m sampling depth.</vertaccr></vertacc></posacc><attracc><attraccr>All attributes appear to be within their intended range or domain.</attraccr></attracc><lineage><srcinfo><typesrc>computer program</typesrc><srccitea>SeineDB</srccitea><srccontr>This microsoft access database provided the tabular datasets used to create both the Sample Locations spatial dataset and the related Sampling results tabular dataset.</srccontr><srctime><srccurr>ground condition</srccurr><timeinfo><rngdates><begdate>20060614</begdate><enddate>20120420</enddate></rngdates></timeinfo></srctime><srccite><citeinfo><origin>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission: Fish and Wildlife Research Institute: South Florida Regional Lab: Finfish Research Program</origin><title>Seine Monitoring database Data Entry Program CORRECT.accdb</title><othercit>These data were delivered to FWRI's Center for Spatial Analysis for conversion to geospatial data on 9/25/2015.</othercit></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><srcinfo><typesrc>paper</typesrc><srccitea>SeineSamplingProtocol</srccitea><srccontr>This protocol document provided metadata documentation for the sampling protocol.</srccontr><srctime><srccurr>publication date</srccurr><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>unknown</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo></srctime><srccite><citeinfo><origin>FWC: FWRI: South Florida Regional Lab: Finfish Research Program</origin><title>Juvenile Snapper Seine Sampling Protocol</title><geoform>document</geoform></citeinfo></srccite></srcinfo><procstep><srcprod>MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_SampleLocs</srcprod><srcused>SeineDB</srcused><srcprod>MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_Samples</srcprod><proccont><cntinfo><cntvoice>(727) 896-8626</cntvoice><cntfax>(727) 893-1679</cntfax><cntemail>Chris.Boland@MyFWC.com</cntemail><cntemail>GISLibrarian@MyFWC.com</cntemail><cntaddr><address>100 Eighth Avenue Southeast</address><address>Mailstation J3N-CAMRA</address><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><city>Saint Petersburg</city><state>Florida</state><postal>33701</postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntperp><cntper>Christopher Boland, GISP</cntper><cntorg>FWC:FWRI:Information Science &amp; Management: Center for Spatial Analysis</cntorg></cntperp><cntpos>Enterprise Geodatabase Administrator</cntpos><hours>Monday - Friday 8AM - 5PM</hours><cntinst>Please forward all data requests to GISLibrarian@MyFWC.com.</cntinst></cntinfo></proccont><procdesc>Data Conversion to Geospatial Data:
Jeff Renchen delivered the SeineDB to Chris Boland on 9/25/2015.  After delivery, Chris Boland completed the following tasks on the data:
1.  Imported the Seine Sampling Locations Table (tbl_physical_master) into a GIS compatible personal geodatabase (.mdb)
2. Converted Month, Day, Year, &amp; StartTime fields into a single Survey Date Time field (SDATE)
3.  Converted the Latitude and Longitude fields from Degrees Decimal Minutes to Decimal Degrees (Lat_DD &amp; Long_DD)
4. Imported the table into GIS, diplayed the data based upon their XY (Long/Lat) pairs, selected points, excluding the Florida Keys pilot project (Survey prefix FKX) and Marquesas pilot project (survey prefix MQM) [as recommended by Finfish Research Program], and projected data into NAD83 (2011) Florida GDL Albers (meter) projection.
5.  Removed survey location "FKM14050108" from dataset, because it was located approximately 2 miles offshore, outside of the survey area.
6. Converted all survey site physical attribute fields to FLOAT datatype, rather than text (Depth, Temperature, pH, Salinity, &amp; Dissolved Oxygen).
7. Created and applied domains for Bottom Type, Bottom Vegetation, and Percent Composition fields.
8. Created a 1-to-many relationship class between MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_SampleLocs feature class and MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_Samples table based upon "Survey" Primary-Foreign key pair.
9. Wrote FGDC-CSDGM compliant metadata.</procdesc><procdate>201509</procdate></procstep><procstep><srcprod>SeineDB</srcprod><proccont><cntinfo><cntvoice>(305) 289-2330</cntvoice><cntaddr><address>South Florida Regional Lab</address><address>2796 Overseas Highway 119</address><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><city>Marathon</city><state>Florida</state><postal>33050</postal><country>USA</country></cntaddr><cntorgp><cntorg>FWC:FWRI:South Florida Regional Lab: Finfish Research Program</cntorg></cntorgp><hours>Monday - Friday 8AM - 5PM</hours></cntinfo></proccont><srcused>SeineSamplingProtocol</srcused><procdesc>Field Sampling and Field Data Collection:
One seine haul will be conducted during daylight hours at each site. Fish collections will be made using a 21.3m center-bag drag offshore seine, constructed of knotless 3.2mm #35 Delta nylon-mesh and a 183cm x 183cm x 183cm bag. The net coverage area is approximately 140 m2/haul. The seine is pulled by hand using PVC poles attached to the ends of the net. For an offshore seine, the net is set perpendicular to the current or wind (whichever is dominant) in water that is at least 0.3m deep. In order to maintain a standardized distance between the end poles a 15.5m line is attached between the tops of the two end poles and kept taught. In order to standardize the distance of the tow two small PVC tether poles with 9.1m of line attached are anchored in the substrate on both sides of the net adjacent to the end poles, the free end of these tether lines are attached to the end poles. The net is then pulled forward 9.1m until the tether lines become taught. At this point the tether lines are dropped and the seine ends are brought together encircling and trapping the fish. The ends of the net are then pulled together 90o around a pivot pole in order to move the fish down into the bag. Then the bag is slowly inverted and the fish are removed and placed in a 5 gallon bucket for processing.
All snappers collected will be counted, measured to the nearest mm, and identified to the lowest possible taxon in the field. This will typically be to species. Young juvenile snapper will be defined as &lt; 100mm standard length (SL), settlement-stage snapper as &lt; 40mm SL, early-stage juveniles as &gt; 20mm to &lt; 40mm SL, and new recruits as &lt; 20mm SL. All other fish collected will be counted, measured, and identified to the lowest possible taxon as well.
Hydrographic data, atmospheric and sea conditions, and observations relative to bottom type including water depth, substrate type, submerged aquatic vegetation (SAV) types, and percent bottom cover of SAV will be recorded at each site. Water temperature (ºC), salinity (‰), dissolved oxygen (mg/L), and pH will be measured using a YSI water-quality instrument. Turbidity will be measured using a secchi disk.
Four randomly selected seagrass quadrats will be visually surveyed at each site following the Braun-Blanquet technique (Braun-Blanquet, 1972) in order to characterize the abundance, density, and frequency of SAV occurring at the site.</procdesc><procdate>Ongoing</procdate></procstep></lineage></dataqual><distinfo><smdistnm>Available without restriction</smdistnm><distliab>This data set is in the public domain, and the recipient may not assert any proprietary rights thereto nor represent it to anyone as other than a Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission produced data set; it is provided "as-is" without warranty of any kind, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. The user assumes all responsibility for the accuracy and suitability of this data set for a specific application. In no event will the staff of the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission be liable for any damages, including lost profits, lost savings, or other incidental or consequential damages arising from the use of or the inability to use this data set.  </distliab><stdorder><fees>None. However, persons or organizations requesting information must provide transfer media if FTP is not available and must pay express shipping costs if express shipping is required.</fees><ordering>Contact GIS Librarian by e-mail, telephone, or letter explaining which products are needed and providing a brief description of how the products will be used. Also, provide name and address of the person or organization requesting the products.</ordering><turnarnd>Usually within 10 business days, although, complex requests may take longer</turnarnd><smdistty>1</smdistty><digform><digtopt><onlinopt><computer><networka><networkr>http://myfwc.com/research</networkr></networka></computer></onlinopt></digtopt><digtinfo><formname>SHP</formname></digtinfo></digform></stdorder><custom>Contact GIS Librarian</custom><resdesc>Downloadable Data</resdesc><distrib><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission-Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</cntorg><cntper>GISLibrarian</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Data Librarian</cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</address><address>100 Eighth Avenue Southeast</address><city>St. Petersburg</city><state>Florida</state><postal>33701</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>727-896-8626</cntvoice><cntfax>727-893-1679</cntfax><cntemail>GISLibrarian@MyFWC.com</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib></distinfo><metainfo><metstdn>FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn><metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv><mettc>local time</mettc><metac>No restrictions on metadata</metac><metuc>Metadata must be distributed with the data set.</metuc><metsi><metscs>FWRI-MC</metscs><metsc>Available</metsc><metshd>Metadata must be distributed with the data set.</metshd></metsi><metd>20150929</metd><metc><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission-Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</cntorg><cntper>GISLibrarian</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Data Librarian</cntpos><cntaddr><addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype><address>Fish and Wildlife Research Institute</address><address>100 Eighth Avenue Southeast</address><city>St. Petersburg</city><state>Florida</state><postal>33701</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>727-896-8626</cntvoice><cntfax>727-893-1679</cntfax><cntemail>GISLibrarian@MyFWC.com</cntemail></cntinfo></metc></metainfo><spdoinfo><direct>Vector</direct><ptvctinf/></spdoinfo><dataIdInfo><envirDesc>Microsoft Windows Server 2008 R2 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.2.2.3552</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode value="eng"/><countryCode value="USA"/></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle>MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_SampleLocs_Wm</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd value="005"/></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="001"/></spatRpType><dataExt><vertEle><vertMinVal>0.000000</vertMinVal><vertMaxVal>1.500000</vertMaxVal></vertEle><geoEle/></dataExt><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="search"><exTypeCode>1</exTypeCode><westBL>-81.113750</westBL><eastBL>-80.942133</eastBL><northBL>24.764333</northBL><southBL>24.685283</southBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng"/><countryCode value="USA"/></mdLang><distInfo><distFormat><formatName>File Geodatabase Feature Class</formatName></distFormat></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName>dataset</mdHrLvName><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode code="3857"/><idCodeSpace>EPSG</idCodeSpace><idVersion>8.2.6</idVersion></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><geometObjs><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd value="004"/></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt>1074</geoObjCnt></geometObjs><topLvl><TopoLevCd value="001"/></topLvl></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><mdDateSt>20151110</mdDateSt><spref><horizsys><planar><mapproj><mapprojn>WGS 1984 Web Mercator Auxiliary Sphere</mapprojn></mapproj><planci><plance>coordinate pair</plance><coordrep><absres>0.0001</absres><ordres>0.0001</ordres></coordrep><plandu>meter</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>D WGS 1984</horizdn><ellips>WGS 1984</ellips><semiaxis>6378137.0</semiaxis><denflat>298.257223563</denflat></geodetic></horizsys></spref><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypd>Juvenile Snapper Seine Sampling Locations</enttypd><enttypds>FWC: FWRI: South Florida Regional Lab: Finfish Research Program</enttypds><enttypl>MiddleKeys_SeineSurveys_SampleLocs_Wm</enttypl></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl><attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Survey</attrlabl><attrdef>Sampling Location Unique ID</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>text</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>StartDepth</attrlabl><attrdef>Start depth of seine station in meters</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>0</rdommin><rdommax>1.5</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Lat_DD</attrlabl><attrdef>Latitude in Decimal Degrees</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>number (double) field</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Long_DD</attrlabl><attrdef>Longitude in Decimal Degrees</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>number (double) field</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>SDate</attrlabl><attrdef>Survey Date/Time</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Date/time field</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Depth_1</attrlabl><attrdef>1st Instrument Depth (meters)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>0.2</rdommin><rdommax>1.2</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Temp_1</attrlabl><attrdef>1st Water Temperature (degrees Celcius)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>13.4</rdommin><rdommax>36.1</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>pH_1</attrlabl><attrdef>1st pH record</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>1</rdommin><rdommax>14</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Salinity_1</attrlabl><attrdef>1st Salinity record (ppt)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>28</rdommin><rdommax>40</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DisO2_1</attrlabl><attrdef>1st Dissolved Oxygen (mg/L) record</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>1.5</rdommin><rdommax>17.0</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Depth_2</attrlabl><attrdef>2nd Depth record (meters)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>0.2</rdommin><rdommax>1.5</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Temp_2</attrlabl><attrdef>2nd Water Temperature (degrees Celcius)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>13.9</rdommin><rdommax>34.8</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>pH_2</attrlabl><attrdef>2nd pH record</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>1</rdommin><rdommax>14</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>Salinity_2</attrlabl><attrdef>2nd Salinity record (ppt)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>28</rdommin><rdommax>40</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>DisO2_2</attrlabl><attrdef>2nd Dissolved Oxygen record (mg/L)</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>1.6</rdommin><rdommax>17</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmType1</attrlabl><attrdef>Primary Bottom Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>C</edomv><edomvd>Corals: Hard</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>D</edomv><edomvd>Detritus</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>H</edomv><edomvd>Shells</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>M</edomv><edomvd>Mud</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>O</edomv><edomvd>Oysters</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>P</edomv><edomvd>Sponge</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>R</edomv><edomvd>Rocks</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>S</edomv><edomvd>Sand</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>T</edomv><edomvd>Tunicates</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>U</edomv><edomvd>Unknown</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>V</edomv><edomvd>Perna viridis (Asian green mussel)</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmType2</attrlabl><attrdef>Secondary Bottom type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmType1 Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmType3</attrlabl><attrdef>Tertiary Bottom Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmType1 Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmType4</attrlabl><attrdef>Quaternary Bottom Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmType1 Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmVeg1</attrlabl><attrdef>Primary Bottom Vegetation Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AB</edomv><edomvd>Acetabularia spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AC</edomv><edomvd>Algae: Calcareous</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AG</edomv><edomvd>Algae: Filamentous green</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AM</edomv><edomvd>Algae: Mixed</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AR</edomv><edomvd>Algae: Filamentous red</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AT</edomv><edomvd>Acanthophora spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>AU</edomv><edomvd>Algae: Unidentified</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>CA</edomv><edomvd>Caulerpa spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GM</edomv><edomvd>Seagrass: Mixed</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>GU</edomv><edomvd>Seagrass: Unidentified</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>HA</edomv><edomvd>Halodule spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>HI</edomv><edomvd>Halophila spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>LA</edomv><edomvd>Laurencia spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>NO</edomv><edomvd>None</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>PE</edomv><edomvd>Penicillus capitatus</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>RU</edomv><edomvd>Ruppia spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SG</edomv><edomvd>Sargassum spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>SY</edomv><edomvd>Syringodium spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>TH</edomv><edomvd>Thalassia spp.</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>UN</edomv><edomvd>Unknown</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BV1_PercComp</attrlabl><attrdef>Primary Bottom Vegetation Percent Composition</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>10%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>20%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>30%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>40%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>50%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>60%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>70%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>80%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>90%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>X</edomv><edomvd>100%</edomvd><edomvds>FWRI</edomvds></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmVeg2</attrlabl><attrdef>Secondary Bottom Vegetation Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmVeg1 codeset.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BV2_PercComp</attrlabl><attrdef>Secondary Bottom Vegetation Percent Composition</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BV1_PercComp Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmVeg3</attrlabl><attrdef>Tertiary Bottom Vegetation Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmVeg1 codeset.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BV3_PercComp</attrlabl><attrdef>Tertiary Bottom Vegetation Percent Composition</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BV1_PercComp Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BttmVeg4</attrlabl><attrdef>Quaternary Bottom Vegetation Type</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BttmVeg1 codeset.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BV4_PercComp</attrlabl><attrdef>Quaternary Bottom Vegetation Percent Composition</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Same as BV1_PercComp Codeset</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>BV_TotalCover</attrlabl><attrdef>Bottom Vegetation Percent Total Cover</attrdef><attrdefs>FWRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>0</rdommin><rdommax>100</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr></detailed></eainfo><Esri><CreaDate>20190529</CreaDate><CreaTime>19475400</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce></Esri></metadata>
